<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:05 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Another Semester Down</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;December 16, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Well, it is finally over. The semester is over. Finally.&#xD;&#xD;I do make it sound like this semester was so very horrible, but in all actuality, it wasn&#x2019;t all that bad. In fact, it kind of got better right at the very end. Turned out &lt;i&gt;everyone &lt;/i&gt;thought that Physics class was terrible (i.e., everyone did horrible on those tests), so I wasn&#x2019;t alone there. Grade curves for the win; I should probably still do fairly well!&#xD;&#xD;Things were quite interesting socially too. I think having us all crammed grouped together in one dorm made us all &lt;i&gt;closer. &lt;/i&gt;Well, maybe for us guys. The girls apparently ran into some slight &lt;i&gt;issues &lt;/i&gt;towards the end, getting on each other&#x2019;s nerves and such /allI&#x2019;msayingonthematter.&#xD;But in all, I guess I am happy there at Stony Brook. While I do miss Southampton for the community we had there and the campus itself, I&#x2019;m also happy about the new Academic Direction I&#x2019;m heading in. This Biology business should hopefully prove to be fruitful in its interesting splendor, and I&#x2019;m also hoping to succeed in the forthcoming classes despite the horror stories I hear about them sometimes.&#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;m not even going to touch upon another often-frequented theme addressed here because, truthfully, I just have no idea anymore. And I have no idea when or where I will &#x2026;have an &#x2026;idea &#x2026;anymore.&#xD;But, er&#x2026; I guess I just did &#x201C;touch upon&#x201D; it. &#xD;Oh well.&#xD;&#xD;Anyway, now that it is finally Winter Break I can finally relax a bit. This vacation should be very nice. I haven&#x2019;t seen my cousins in like X amount of years, where X stands for the amount of years I haven&#x2019;t seen them. (What.) And yes, this is a vacation. Apparently some people were a bit &lt;i&gt;confused &lt;/i&gt;by the last post in thinking I was insinuating that I was actually moving to Florida. What is that I don&#x2019;t even.&#xD;It will also be hilarious yet again to see Cody&#x2019;s reaction to being with the X-TREME AMOUNT of other dogs (3) at my grandma&#x2019;s. Last time we were there, he hid away in my parents&#x2019; room on the bed and was terrified up until the last day whereupon he finally started to play with the other dogs. We left shortly after. It was so sad. But then we showed up at my other grandma&#x2019;s house and he entered a state of euphoric bliss which resulted in many Grandma Kisses (or licks. Whatever you see them as.)&#xD;We&#x2019;ll see what happens this time around.&#xD;&#xD;So yep, I shan&#x2019;t probably post anything new until like, New Years maybe. Who knows. NO ONE DOES. That&#x2019;s right. But if that&#x2019;s the case, then:&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;i&gt;Happy Holidays!&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;                                                 &#x2013;K.Doyle&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
