<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 22:59:57 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&#x201C;Kevin Listens To&#x2026;&#x201D; I</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;July 31, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>So yes, welcome to this new exciting series to froof up my oh so interesting blog! (&#x2026;I just realized now that exclamation points look awfully like Is or lowercase ls. That is, &#x201C;eyes&#x201D; and &#x201C;elles&#x201D;, respectfully; seeing as THOSE LOOK THE SAME TOO. But this font&#x2019;s cool, so I have no choice but to keep it. &lt;/rant&gt;)&#xD;&#xD;This song is the second-to-last song in Train&#x2019;s new album, Save Me, San Francisco; and I have to say, I was not too crazy about it at first. It kind of seemed&#x2026; too slow and that it didn&#x2019;t really go anywhere. But after listening to it a certain number of additional times, I took notice of it&#x2019;s &lt;i&gt;simple charm&lt;/i&gt; combined with the nice lyrics revolving around The Narrator (can you refer to the singer of a song as The Narrator, capital letters and all?) complimenting the &lt;i&gt;apple of his eye&lt;/i&gt; by using &lt;i&gt;clever metaphors &lt;/i&gt;to compare her to pleasurable things.&#xD;&#xD;What I had(ve) just recently taken noticeable note of was how the mood of the song essentially changes towards the end with the initial surprise drum mashings and powerful piano and guitar riffs. And then those trumpets; can&#x2019;t forget those trumpets.&#xD;&#xD;I feel almost as if this is &lt;i&gt;symbolic &lt;/i&gt;in some way or another. Like, there are some underlying problems in The Narrator&#x2019;s situation which are then &#x201C;expressed&#x201D; via this musical-rampage at the end. Or maybe I am looking too much into this. But, then again, is that not what one should do with songs?&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Alright, that concludes this segment of KLT! (ProTip: exclamation point)&#xD;Tune in next time for episode II, because I know you all read this blog religiously. &#xD;All &#x2264;1 of you.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
