<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:07 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Tragedy and Hilarity Combine?!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;January 12, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Earlier this morning after logging onto my &lt;i&gt;precious MacBook&#x2122;, &lt;/i&gt;I perform my usual routine. Part of this includes checking my Mail, which I do, and I see that Nicole (who now is&lt;i&gt; large and in charge &lt;/i&gt;of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://theothersideofouruniverse.tumblr.com/"&gt;this here blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;) has some new blog posts in my RSS feed&#x2014;hooray! I proceed to read them, ending on the most recent one being titled: I HAD A DREAM I WAS OBESE, among other, many, posts of obscure pictures that at the time did not seem strange to be posted on Nicole&#x2019;s blog. (I was still reeling from the intense Snowventure of this morning, freeing our driveway from the chilling grip of the recent Snowpocalypse, so forgive my misjudgment.)&#xD;&#xD;So, I see she is online as well, i.e., on &lt;i&gt;AOL Instant Messenger &lt;/i&gt;(iChat for me cause Macs rox my sox) and I decide to playfully initiate the conversation based upon the aforementioned blog post:&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;so how's that whole being obese thing going for you?&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;ive been obese since age 9, its not going well xD&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;lolol; I can't say that I've ever had a dream where my body size had become overexcessivly large before&#xD;what's that even &lt;i&gt;like? &lt;/i&gt;are you imagining (aka dreaming) that and you are all ABDHEJFJD&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;well both my parents struggle with weight so i do everything in my power not to&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;well I really don't think that's an issue you have to worry about&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;considering i hardly eat, nope xD&#xD;im just not a hungry person&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;but food tastes good!&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;i know&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;And then we continued to discuss matters pertaining to food, The Universe, and giving ProTips.&#xD;The conversation seemed to start off just fine with us jokingly discussing the absurdly made post about having fat dreams. Nothing seemed out of the ordinary, nothing at all.&#xD;&#xD;Much later in the day, after night had fallen over the softly fallen snow of early morn, we started discussing blogs. Me being the &lt;i&gt;flashy showoff &lt;/i&gt;that I am &lt;/hyperbole&gt;, I sent Nicole a screenshot of my Mail&#x2019;s RSS feed and how I was able to read her blog posts through there. After viewing the image, she exclaimed in a capslock-fuled fury: &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;WHAT THATS NOT MY BLOG LMAO&#xD;&#xD;to which I replied:&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;it's the RSS version!1!&#xD;[&#x2026;]&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;whereupon I can read The Entries&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Oh how blissfully unaware I was. And this proceeded to happen:&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;but w8 where is the other posts?! the "obese dream" one?&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;dude&#xD;on tumblr you can change your urls&#xD;so i changed mine&#xD;and youve been subscribed to the new person who took my url&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;WHAT&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;YOUVE BEEN STALKING THIS GIRL WHOSE NAME IS GABRIELLA&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;WOAH&#xD;&lt;b&gt;WOAH&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;[&#x2026;]&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;MIND BLOWN; I HAD NO IDEA&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;HAHAHAHAHA DID YOU REALIZE THATS NOT WHAT I NORMALLY TALK ABOUT&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;so the obese dream wasn't you?!?!?!&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Nicole &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;WHAT OBESE DREAM&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Me &lt;/b&gt;&#xD;OH FUCK&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;NEEDLESS TO SAY, I felt like &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://urbandictionary.com/urthenoob"&gt;The Noob.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Luckily this all went down &#x201C;so well&#x201D; too! Nicole could have very well been all &#x201C;GTFO&#x201D; at me first thing in the morning, leaving me very confused! It is a good thing no angrystrife arose due to this (despite my relentless &#x201C;OMG I AM SO SORRY&#x201D;s and &#x201C;SHITSHITHISHITHISHITHISTHIOMGSHIT&#x201D;s)&#xD;&#xD; But now after all is said and done, we both now have quite the hi-larious story to tell! &#x2026;Which is exactly what I am doing right now!&#xD;&#xD;Oh yeah, and she is also never going to let me live this down. As can be seen &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://theothersideofouruniverse.tumblr.com/post/2725343938/how-i-was-diagnosed-with-derpression"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Among all the other, um, &lt;i&gt;incidents &lt;/i&gt;that happened during today&#x2019;s conversation.&#xD;        &#xD;fffffuuuuuu&#x2013;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
