<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:05 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>New Plans for a New Year</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;January 3, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Ah yes, the year Two Thousand Eleven Anno Domini, how I welcome you with great &lt;i&gt;joie de vivre. &lt;/i&gt;This year&#x2019;s already off to an interesting start, among other things that I hope to foresee happening. But first I will apprise unto you my tale of the Car That Did Not Start.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;Story&gt;&#xD;&#xD;As you may know, I had taken a vacation to the Sunshine State that is Florida. My family and I spent Christmas there at my grandmother&#x2019;s house. Things were very nice there: Cody didn&#x2019;t freak out as much as last time, and I was able to spend precious time with members of my extended family (because Time is the most important treasure one can possess). So, anyway, after our adventures at my grandma&#x2019;s we left to go spend New Years with my other grandma in South Carolina. Upon our arrival, we were quite surprised. It was snowing. It is not supposed to snow in regions that are denoted with the word SOUTH.&#xD;&#xD;Once getting over the fact that we&#x2019;re heading into the next ice age (which according to my Archaeology professor is &#x201C;good for our species&#x201D;), we did a multitude of things, including getting to see my mom having to cope with my grandma (her mom), which is always hilarious. Finally New Years arrived and pretty much everyone was already half asleep. Champagne was distributed to the awake patrons, along with orange juice mixed with the aforementioned alcohol, transforming the otherwise extremely potent beverage into a better-tasting mimosa. After downing the drink, it was off to bed because we were leaving bright and early in the morning! (Which, ironically, was so early that it wasn&#x2019;t even bright.)&#xD;&#xD;I begrudgingly woke up around six in the morning, getting roughly as much sleep as I did a night prior on a Skype session that lasted from two in the morning until five. I had performed my morning routine of hygienic practices (e.g., brushing teeth) and walked into the living room to overhear some distraught conversing. I couldn&#x2019;t quite imagine what might have been wrong here, and after being abruptly told inquiring about the situation, I found out that our car would not start despite the fact it had started the day before.&#xD;&#xD;The only logical answer to this precarious problem was that the battery needed to be jumped. We prepared my late grandfather&#x2019;s (and now grandmother&#x2019;s) &lt;a href="http://www.chrysler.com/en/2010/pt_cruiser/"&gt;PT Cruiser&#xAE;&lt;/a&gt; to be set up for the process. To our surprise (again), we found out that our car was still not starting. Guessing that there must be a problem with the battery, we called a mechanic who sold us a new battery. So we then replace our battery with the new one and problem solved, right?&#xD;&#xD;Nope. The car still wouldn&#x2019;t start. So now we have absolutely no idea what the problem could be. We had the car towed to the mechanics where they looked to try and find out what was wrong. After a while (around noon I believe) they settle on a diagnosis: there was something wrong with the car&#x2019;s security system. The car apparently has a system that will read a microchip imbedded somewhere in the car key to make sure the key it legitimate or not. You know, to prevent someone who painstakingly somehow made a copy of your car key without your knowledge and then somehow broke into your car, ready to set their foolproof plan into action only to find out that today&#x2019;s day-and-age technology has bested them! The fake-real key won&#x2019;t work because it lacks the special chip inside it that probably has never done anything other than allow a malfunctioning security system to believe it&#x2019;s fake.&#xD;&#xD;After a rousing round of &#x201C;FFFFUUUUUU&#x2014;&#x201D;s all around, we decide waiting around for the car to be taken to the dealer (which was closed on New Years Day) would probably get us home by next weekend, so we decide to Rent-A-Car&#x2122;.&#xD;We procure the assistance of some car whose identity alludes me, filled it up with our stuff, and head home right then and there. Mind you, it&#x2019;s now around 3 PM, when we were supposed to leave at 6 AM. &#xD;&#xD;We finally arrive home after a night&#x2019;s stay in some hotel after already renting a room online in a hotel farther away because we couldn&#x2019;t bear to stay on the road any longer. What is to become of our precious car that we abandoned down south you may ask? My father is to fly down there once it is repaired and then drive it all the way back up here. Fun, right?&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/Story&gt;&#xD;&#xD;Anyway, it&#x2019;s really nice to be home now. I had my first guitar lesson with my old lesson teacher today and I learned that I have been holding the guitar neck like a noob, which prevented me from playing bar chords! I could not understand why my pointer finger would never sit correctly across the fret before acquiring this knowledge. &lt;b&gt;Knowledge is power&lt;/b&gt;.&#xD;&#xD;While on the topic of knowledge (transition! See what I did there?), this upcoming semester starts my Biological Undertakings! Excitement flows through my very veins (and arteries. And capillaries). The academic nightmare that was last semester coughphysicscough yielded some fairly nice grades after all, though! I was very relieved to see that curve in physics wasn&#x2019;t just a load of horseshit. Now it&#x2019;s time to take on the &lt;b&gt;real classes &lt;/b&gt;I need. I am prepared; bring it on.&#xD;&#xD;This year should hopefully hold other nice things to come. I am already now thinking of pursuing some things which, if they work out, could be fun. Also now that if I learn enough guitar knowledge, I might possess the power needed to finally form that band with Marc and a drummer who still doesn&#x2019;t exist yet! (&#x2026;That&#x2019;s a hint to apply if you are interested which I know you are oh so much yes you are interested.)&#xD;&#xD;Anyway, here&#x2019;s to the new year! We&#x2019;ll see how things play out as &lt;i&gt;the days go by&lt;/i&gt;. All 365 of them.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Update:&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Oh shit. I just realized none of you can read the fancy font I used in writing that really big HAPPY HOLIDAYS at the end of my last entry. I fixed that with my dubious method used before to fix the site&#x2019;s name. Go check it out again and gawk at its beauty.&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
