<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:07 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Third Quarter Analysis Spreadsheets</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;January 8, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Yesterday I re-watched the last episode of season seven of The Office and I realized that they really didn&#x2019;t do a &#x201C;good job&#x201D; of making any attempts to write Michael out of the script, seeing as this was Mr. Carell&#x2019;s last season on the show. And yes, it&#x2019;s apparently official that he&#x2019;s leaving, seeing as he was quoted as stating exactly: &lt;i&gt;&#x201C;lolol yep I am leaving; there are so many good peeple still there so like the show will be just fine!1!.&#x201D;&lt;/i&gt;[citation needed]&lt;i&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;And that&#x2019;s like saying the human body will be fine after you remove the spine, because there are still &lt;i&gt;so many&lt;/i&gt; important parts that make up the body, like the feet, arms, head, liver, and kidneys, that the body will continue to do fine without it! Perfect, unflawed logic right there.&#xD;&#xD;Maybe he &lt;i&gt;will &lt;/i&gt;miraculously return later on somehow, and the whole leaving thing can just be a part of the plot. That probably won&#x2019;t happen though. People just don&#x2019;t come back like that. It&#x2019;s a shame too, because I would have liked to see the series go to completion without anyone bailing out on it, letting it slowly decay while it straps on its water skis and launches itself over a ferocious sea creature.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;EDIT:&#xD;LOL OOPS I AM SO DUMB THE SEASON ISN&#x2019;T OVER YET I AM DUMB DUMB STUPID DUMB. &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;So I guess then they will write him out. NEVER MIND.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
