<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120818" date="2012-08-18 00:18:40 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Things &#x201C;R&#x201D; Good</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;January 24, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>        I have come to realize over this past year how lucky I really am. I went from totally miserable to the happiest I&#x2019;ve ever been, and that would never have happened if all those Series of Unfortunate Events never took place! For instance, i.e., e.g., i.e.g., if my school did not get shut down by The Man, I would have never gone to Stony Brook&#x2019;s wonderful Main Campus and subsequently joined their wind ensemble and then started talking to Nicole! We oftentimes discuss alternate timeline whereupon Southampton did not close and she decided to pursue her interest in the environmental sciences and then she would have went there too but like we might not have even really talked in that case and like aahjsaghdgsahjdhsajk! The thought is frightening. But she tells me, and I quote&lt;b&gt;*&lt;/b&gt; &#x201C;yeah, fuck the sciences; teaching little childrens is much more rewarding. LOL&#x201D; &#xD;        Regardless of this fact, we have been doing quite well! It&#x2019;s nigh on one year now that we&#x2019;ve been together, and &lt;i&gt;what a year it was.&lt;/i&gt; Most peeps should have at least had &lt;i&gt;some &lt;/i&gt;form of tiffs or quarrels between them in a year but we haven&#x2019;t! We can&#x2019;t find anything to get mad at each other over! Of course now you all will be all JUMPING UP on good ol&#x2019; Murphy&#x2019;s Law here and say &#x201C;LOL NOW YOU WILL THAT YOU&#x2019;VE SAID THAT&#x201D; but no, even Murphy cannot influence things&#x2014;not even normal life occurrences, and this all has to do with my Thesis of &#x201C;my girlfriend is always right.&#x201D; She had self-designated this thesis to me, and after some observations, I have some data that proves this. FOR EXAMPLE: we went to eat at a restaurant and gave our name for the wait. We then went out to Walk on the Town for like, a time, and me being me was all &#x201C;GOMGMO what if they call our name while we&#x2019;re not in there?!?!?!?!&#x201D; and she&#x2019;s all &#x201C;THEY WON&#x2019;T; IT&#x2019;S FINE.&#x201D; and turns out we did not miss our seat-calling. &#xD;&#xD;&lt;i&gt;But I digress. &#xD;&#xD;        &lt;/i&gt;Our one-year anniversary together is coming up in February which is, of course, when school&#x2019;s in session! The current plan is to take the intrepid journey up to the frost forsaken land of Potsdam, where temperatures delve so cold it makes even the Kelvin scale cry, so I can be there at least sometime during that month. I fear I might not survive the journey up there, though; having to scale the frozen peaks of the Adirondacks. Poor Stella most likely won&#x2019;t be able to brave this trip, so I will have to take The Mountaineer, whose name oddly fits with the terrain that I&#x2019;ll be driving across. As it seems currently, we look good for hopefully many more years into the future!&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;I think I can say with confidence that this is the happiest I have been in a while, if not ever.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;*&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;note: quote is not verbatim&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;I have also obtained yet &lt;i&gt;another &lt;/i&gt;new Music Artist-Group who is quite splendid &lt;i&gt;as well. &lt;/i&gt;They are&#x2026; &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;The Weepies&lt;/b&gt;. &#xD;Holy fuck. Yeah. &#xD;&#xD;        Sarah, who you all read about way back in my story about my lost sweatshirt, had posted a cryptic message on my Facebook Wall Timeline that read &#x201C;Yo bro, listen to the weepies!&#x201D; At the time, I had no idea what these &#x201C;weepies&#x201D; were. I thought they might have been some otherworldly entity that she was suggesting I take advice from. For what reasons I needed this advice I did not know. I disregarded these words for a while before I decided to take action and call her out on this mysterious phrase. Right after I did this, I had the bright idea to just search the term &#x201C;the weepies&#x201D; online and, lo and behold, I found out they were a band. I felt very foolish as the rest of that conversation with Sarah unfolded.&#xD;&#xD;        In time I came to possess their two most recent albums. After countless listen-throughs, I can state that they are like REALLY GOOD OH MY GOD. Their melodies are &lt;i&gt;so fresh and so pure they warm my soul. &lt;/i&gt;Maybe I&#x2019;ll do another &#x201C;Kevin Listens To&#x201D; of their music. I haven&#x2019;t done one of those since October of 2010! &#x2026;Holy shit, it&#x2019;s been that long?! I really don&#x2019;t post things too often here! But I guess that was always the way I wanted this thing to work: occasional posts with a decent amount of words in them that were pleasant to read! I did not want it to be like the infernal &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tumblr&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: the bane of my entire blogging existence.&#xD;&#xD;        So yeah. I finish up this shorter-than-I-wanted-it-to-be-for-a-3-almost-4-month hiatus as I sit here at my school desk, all too ready to start yet another wonderful semester here at SBU. Two days in and it doesn&#x2019;t seem so bad &#x2026;yet. We&#x2019;ll see though. Hopefully I will actually write things more often! &lt;i&gt;LOL.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
