<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:08 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>303: The Musical, Act II</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;February 14, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>A new semester has started, and on a quite promising note at that! I speculate many good things are to happen throughout the course of the rest of the term. I think I can say that I&#x2019;m experiencing this feeling called &#x201C;happiness&#x201D; once again; something I haven&#x2019;t truly felt in quite some time, honestly, even before some certain events transpired. Coinciding with these refreshing feelings, I&#x2019;m &lt;b&gt;finally &lt;/b&gt;taking classes pertaining to my new major of Biology Skylark: Studier of the Living World.&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;I&#x2019;m now &lt;i&gt;excited &lt;/i&gt;to be taking these classes, despite how arduous some of these upcoming classes will supposedly be. (Here&#x2019;s looking at you, Organic-Chemistry.) I really do hope I&#x2019;ll be able to put myself through taking all these classes in a somewhat significantly shorter period of time. I&#x2019;m hoping my &lt;i&gt;tenacious spirit &lt;/i&gt;will be enough to get through it all.&#xD;&#xD;Speaking of &lt;i&gt;tenacious spirits, &lt;/i&gt;I will REALLY be needing this to deal with the many shenanigans that Kenny has been spewing this semester. He pretty much specializes in the Art of Annoying, but, he &lt;b&gt;does it so well that you can&#x2019;t actually be mad at him! &lt;/b&gt;It&#x2019;s actually quite hilarious, all while causing many a-facepalms. This especially applies to Marc. Kenny and Marc seem to be fated to be enemies. Their first encounter was apparently Kenny hitting Marc in the face with a frisbee, and then it&#x2019;s all been &#x201C;downhill&#x201D; ever since. It&#x2019;s still hilarious to see their interactions, nonetheless. For instance, right now! Kenny is currently &lt;i&gt;lounging on my bed &lt;/i&gt;(which he normally does on Marc&#x2019;s bed. It&#x2019;s become a certain meme of his to do).&#xD;&#xD;In conclusion, I feel this semester will be very nice, relating to all the many nice new things that have developed over the course of recently. I will now wrap up this entry whilst listening to Kenny annoy Marc and potentially have Kenny stay here all throughout the night annoying us because he will never leave. He actually did this one night. &lt;b&gt;He never left. &lt;/b&gt;We pretty much lost our sanity; it was that bad. &#x2026;But oddly hilarious at the same time O__O&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Edit: &lt;/b&gt;I JUST had to break out my first-aid kid to bandage Marc&#x2019;s wounds he received from shenanigans involving Kenny. SHIT JUST HIT THE WHIRLING DEVICE HERE.&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
