<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:08 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>ACADEMIC S.O.S.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;February 27, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I&#x2019;m sending this out there now; I don&#x2019;t have much time left before it completely takes over. This semester is not going as swimmingly as I had hoped. There is an overabundance of &lt;b&gt;mathematics &lt;/b&gt;present. EVERYWHERE. Starting off with &lt;i&gt;General Chemistry II&lt;/i&gt;, so far all we&#x2019;ve done is MATH. And EQUATIONS. Normally this wouldn&#x2019;t be so bad, except for the fact that IT&#x2019;S NEVER EXPLAINED WELL ENOUGH. We&#x2019;re expected to just perfectly extrapolate how to go about doing things and then we&#x2019;re tested on it soon after, with only two or three exams/chances to not fail!&#xD;&#xD;And if I was so horribly mistaken about my expectations regarding chemistry, then I don&#x2019;t even know how to describe how wrong I was about &lt;i&gt;Calculus B&lt;/i&gt;. I mean, the whole course is only TWO CHAPTERS of the entire book! How bad could that be, right? Integrals. Big deal, they&#x2019;re just finding the derivative in reverse! WELL NOPE, THIS IS DIFFICULT TOO. The concepts on how to go about finding the integrals of (relatively simplistic) equations is conveyed and understood with flawless ease, whereas when you actually go and look at a problem, say, on this practice test that I woefully hold in my possession, you HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IS GOING ON. There are exponents raised to exponents raised to exponents WITH A TRIG IDENTITY THROWN IN THERE FOR SHITS N&#x2019; GIGGLES. We were never explicitly shown how to go about finding the integral of a function such as &#x222B;&#x192;(&lt;i&gt;e&lt;/i&gt;^3(x-1))&lt;i&gt;e&lt;/i&gt;^3(x-1)&lt;i&gt;dx &lt;/i&gt;from 1 to 1+ln(4)&#xD;Oh and that&#x2019;s right, we can&#x2019;t even use a calculator to help with algebraic nonsense that, under normal conditions, wouldn&#x2019;t be so hard to do but when you&#x2019;re mind is FREAKING OUT you start screwing up on these things resulting in a large &lt;b&gt;F&lt;/b&gt;.&#xD;&#xD;And then when you thought it couldn&#x2019;t get worse, you find out that BOTH CHEMISTRY AND CALCULUS COMBINE to form INTEGRATED RATE LAWS. IT&#x2019;S A NIGHTMARE COME TRUE!!! THEY&#x2019;RE EVERYWHERE&#x2014;I CAN&#x2019;T ESCAPE THEM! SHIT, HERE THEY COME NOW&#x2014;AAHHRHH--(1/[A])=(1/[A]0)+&lt;i&gt;kt&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;  &#xD;&lt;/i&gt;lim&#x2211;[(2j/n)(&lt;i&gt;e&lt;/i&gt;^(2j/n)^2)]2/n  &#x222B;(sin(x))^2(cos (x))^3 &lt;i&gt;dx&lt;/i&gt;  -&lt;i&gt;d&lt;/i&gt;[A]/&lt;i&gt;dt&lt;/i&gt;=&lt;i&gt;k&lt;/i&gt;[A]&#xD;#initialize some vars $complete="FU";$z=0; $score=0;$score2=0; ERR: NON VALID ANS. SYSTEM REBOOT=YES$^2&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026; ... . .. ..&#xD;.. . .. ...   .&#xD;.  .    . .    .&#xD;.      .            .&#xD;.       .&#xD;.&#xD;&#xD;.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;.&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
