<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 22:59:55 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Oh jegus what was i thinking</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;June 10, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Silly me, posting lyrics vaguely pertaining to how I am feeling when those emotions should not be expressed at this point in time. Now, you may be thinking &#x201C;oh jeez what DID he mean by those wurdz?!?&#x201D;, or you may have some idea as to what they meant but PUT THOSE THOUGHTS OUT OF YOUR HEAD UNTIL THE MOM&#xC9;NT ARISES. Ugh. I feel all subdued right now; i.e., I know of events that shall pass and they can turn either way: one direction is good, and one direction ends slowly in a dismal demise of fate. (Yes, I killed the alliteration there. Oh well).&#xD;&#xD;And all whilst coping &lt;i&gt;internally&lt;/i&gt; with the &lt;i&gt;juicy details&lt;/i&gt; mentioned in the previous &#xB6;, I must trudge and toil through Work. Ah, yes; work. Glorious work. None of that was sarcasm of course because I am making oodles upon oodles of &lt;a href="http://www.mspaintadventures.com/?s=6&amp;p=002782"&gt;boondollars&lt;/a&gt; at work (please to be clicking on the term for a visual explanation in case you do not understand what I am referring to. Which you don&#x2019;t).&#xD;&#xD;But, alas, this all ends once it is time to return to school; which, of course, isn&#x2019;t &lt;i&gt;my &lt;/i&gt;school anymore. That got shut down. But that&#x2019;s old news and I must move on. Hopefully new opportunities will arise over at the joyous Stony Brook Campus. (After all, I &lt;i&gt;do &lt;/i&gt;get to become a Saxophonist once again. Which reminds me, I should practice). I just wonder how many of my newly-made acquaintances in Southampton will stay at &#x201C;main&#x201D; campus in the proceeding years&#x2026; Why, oh why, do I have a bad feeling about this. Oooohhh weell. This (potentially) won&#x2019;t be the first time I&#x2019;d have to start all over with something. (Did I just allude to something there? :o Are you getting pissed off that I am alluding to Paragraph [&#xB6;] One up there: the very thing I do not wish to divulge right now but continue to hint at because it is bothering me so much?!?!?)&#xD;&#xD;*Sigh* &#xD;So, look at this; I just realized this is another one of those serious (albeit less angry) posts. I do guess I need some o&#x2018; these from time to time, though. I mean, that&#x2019;s what makes this a &lt;i&gt;Blog, &lt;/i&gt;amirite? &#xD;Well, alright; I&#x2019;m done venting what I need to. Now I am going to go off to sleep, and dream about who knows what, in order to prepare for Work tomorrow!!!&#xD;&#x2026;At least tomorrow&#x2019;s Friday. I can look forward to the weekend after that, despite not knowing what shenanigans will occur as of yet.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;3 Always (lolwut), &#xD;&#x2013;Doyleboy&#x2028; </richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
