<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:11 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Hey Look, An Update!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;October 1, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>    Sup my broskis! Man, it&#x2019;s been a while since I&#x2019;ve been able to write anything here&#x2026; And yes, I do mean &lt;i&gt;able.&lt;/i&gt; I&#x2019;ve been exceptionally busy since school&#x2019;s started up again! Also no new hilarious antics have happened to inspire any sort of story writing. School is starting to become &#x201C;for the serious,&#x201D; as I believe I&#x2019;ve mentioned in my last post or something; and also everyone of us is almost all gone (and by &#x201C;us&#x201D; I mean us Southamptoners). Next year it will only be my grade-year left; everyone else will have moved on&#x2026; It will be so sad; no one will be left to carry on our legacy&#x2026;&#xD;    Semicolons aside, the School Front is going quite well this semester (for once). Have I mentioned the research work I&#x2019;ve been doing at school? If not, I am now. I&#x2019;m working under my professor in one of the labs here on the lovely hallowed grounds of Stony Brook. She, in turn, is working under the head lab PI Dr. Steven Baines. Maybe you&#x2019;ve heard of him (you probably haven&#x2019;t). There&#x2019;s even a website for this lab, and we all have our pictures on it! Or at least we will; it&#x2019;s still a work in-progress. For any who are interested, &lt;a href="http://life.bio.sunysb.edu/ee/baineslab/"&gt;here&#x2019;s the link&lt;/a&gt;. It&#x2019;s so exciting; I&#x2019;m on the Internet! I&#x2019;m famous! &#x2026;Oh wait.&#xD;    Coinciding with the work I&#x2019;ve been doing, I&#x2019;ve been thinking about future plans for this site. Maybe one day I&#x2019;ll also add a section with any science-endeavors I&#x2019;m participating in and/or am pursuing. This would add more breadth to the site and henceforth increase its monetary value at least 10 fold!!! &#x2026;Not that I really give all to big of a flying crap about that. But yes, I can also say I&#x2019;ve been thinking about the future on a big-picture scale as well. I mean, undergraduate-funtimes are almost over! The Working World is waiting right around the corner! (As well as a fuckton more of schooling, since I &lt;i&gt;am &lt;/i&gt;planning on going All The Way. Dr. Doyle, anybody? Fyea.) I&#x2019;ve been thinking about how things will play out when it&#x2019;s time to go for my graduate degree. Possibly getting an apartment somewhere&#x2026; Going to school while working&#x2026; Good stuff.&#xD;&#xD;But all this has to be taken &lt;i&gt;one step at a time, &lt;/i&gt;as the clich&#xE9; saying goes, and I can say I&#x2019;m looking quite forward to it all as well. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
