<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:02 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&#x201C;Kevin Listens To&#x2026;&#x201D; II</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;October 28, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Oh man, yes, this second installment of this amazing series is covering a WHOLE FREAKING ALBUM. That is how good it is. The song above is the first song on the album, Schizophrenia. It is a fast-tempo&#x2019;d all-around awesome song. The very difficult and fast piano melody almost feels a bit Asian-themed for me (not that that&#x2019;s bad), but that&#x2019;s just me. And then yes, of course, it&#x2019;s a song about some dude with Schizophrenia. What is this I don&#x2019;t even.&#xD;&#xD;Anyway, after this song comes a huge-large assortment of other awesome songs; none of the songs on this album are of &#x201C;meh&#x201D; quality. Other &#x201C;critics&#x201D; have said the same thing1. You, my wonderful readers, should definitely go purchase this album (if you&#x2019;re into this music, that is.) I have already converted one (possibly another. You know who you are) into buying it. I have used my stupendous Powers of Persuasion (and alliteration) to get said person(s) to buy this album. Muhaha.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;And also I mean like look at that artwork right there; it is so astounding! So simple, so quaint, so perfectly fitting! IT IS ALL GREAT GO BUY IT NOW. HERE IS THEIR WEBSITE: &lt;a href="http://www.jukeboxtheghost.com/"&gt;CLICK ON THIS HYPERLINK.&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;So um, yes; I guess that concludes the second installment of &#x201C;Kevin Listens To&#x2026;&#x201D;&#xD;Join us (me) next time! I have a myriad of music to discuss for the future for you all to enjoy!</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
