<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:01 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Why I&#x2019;m Not Allowed At Airports Anymore</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;October 9, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="9_Why_Im_Not_Allowed_At_Airports_Anymore_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="395px" height="210px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>It was approximately three years ago when my family and I had taken our summer vacation trip to Disney World in the marvelous state of Florida. I have relatives in Florida too, grandparents, aunt/uncle/cousins, so we decided to spend a few weeks visiting them before galavanting off to a youthful Disney-filled adventure; that of which I never fully ever experienced&#xD;(I say &#x201C;fully&#x201D; because the last time I had been to Disney World was when I was like, two years old. I had no idea what was going on then!)&#xD;&#xD;During the pre-Disney visit to my grandma&#x2019;s home, we somehow came up with the idea of going to visit the &lt;i&gt;Fountain of Youth. &lt;/i&gt;All I really remember were peacocks. White ones. Everywhere. At least, I think they were everywhere. &#xD;&#x2026;To be honest, I don&#x2019;t even remember the fountain itself at all. I also think they were serving&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;(yes, &lt;i&gt;serving&lt;/i&gt;) little paper cups of the fountain water to drink; y&#x2019;know, in order to become &lt;i&gt;forever young&lt;/i&gt;. Well, it didn&#x2019;t work. And it just tasted like sulfur. Which I am not too sure if that was a health hazard to drink or not.&#xD;&#xD;After the shenanigans, it was time to head over to the Gift Shop! I could not possibly think of what glorious trinkets could await me there. To my surprise, they had a miniature cutlass--just like the ones pirates have! It looked like it came straight out of a &lt;i&gt;Pirates of the Caribbean &lt;/i&gt;movie, I swear. Needless to say, I purchases the aforementioned sword. And by sword, I mean letter opener, because that is what this thing actually was. It&#x2019;s not the most &lt;i&gt;amazing &lt;/i&gt;piece in my sword collection (yes, I collect swords. +5 to your KevFactz!), but I can pretend that it&#x2019;s sharp to make it seem more impressive.&#xD;&#xD;So after purchasing said sword, we returned back to my grandma&#x2019;s house whereupon I hastily threw the sword into my Carry-On Bag in order to avert attention from it. You see, my two cousins (who are brothers) were young at the time and I, as well as my parents, did not want them playing around with a potentially dangerous object.&#xD;&#xD;We spent the rest of our time at my grandma&#x2019;s until we left to go stay at Disney. In order to get the whole experience and whatnot, it is &lt;i&gt;imperative &lt;/i&gt;that one resides on Disney property, of course. Days passed, and days turned to weeks; weeks turned to months&#x2026;&#xD;Okay, not really; we only stayed there a maximum of two weeks I think. During that time, our room&#x2019;s celling fan lost a blade while it was on while we were sleeping and almost decapitated my mom too! We tried to tell the staff about it; they just blamed us for breaking the fan. &lt;i&gt;Staff.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xD;That story aside, we blissfuly spent the rest of our time having fun in the various assortment of Disney parks until it was time to leave. We packed up all our belongings that were strewn all about the room (there weren&#x2019;t many) and left for the airport. We went through the long, drawn out process of making sure you&#x2019;re not a threat to national security, including checking our bags and such, and then it was time to send our Carry-On Bags through the x-ray (or whatever rays they use) machine. I had placed my one Carry-On onto the x-ray ramp-moving-thing and went on my way through the make-sure-you-didn&#x2019;t-place-dangerous-metal-objects-in-your-body machine (which I passed through just fine).&#xD;&#xD;After standing on the other side of the long, drawn-out named machine, we noticed security was carefully studying the machine&#x2019;s display. And my bag hadn&#x2019;t come out of said machine yet&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;Sure enough, one of the intimidating security men walks over with--yes!--my bag. He solemnly asks: &#x201C;&lt;b&gt;Is this yours.&lt;/b&gt;&#x201D; to which I reply &#x201C;Yes.&#x201D; with a bit of a curiously snide tone to my voice because, &lt;i&gt;what possibly could be the problem with my bag? &lt;/i&gt;Well, after my contemptuous &#x201C;yes,&#x201D; Mr. Man here unzips the bag and pulls out my beloved pirate letter-opener cutlass. He then thrusts the sheath off of it and checks the blade with his fingers, presumably realizing that the blade is not actually sharp at all. Bewildered, I stand there, completely in shock that I forgot to take it out of my bag from oh so long ago at my grandmas. Oh, how so long ago it felt. I may never get to go back there again; my life in prison was going to be so very horrible and lonely. (P.S., I didn&#x2019;t actually go to prison.) &#xD;&#xD;My dad then freaks about about how I&#x2019;m &lt;i&gt;going to lose the sword, &lt;/i&gt;and not about how &lt;i&gt;they all think we&#x2019;re potential terrorists now&lt;/i&gt; and that we really &lt;i&gt;could &lt;/i&gt;have gone to jail. The security man then tells us to &#x201C;&lt;b&gt;Wait here.&lt;/b&gt;&#x201D; and he goes off to who the hell knows. My mom then positively thinks: &#x201C;Oh, maybe he&#x2019;s checking whether or not to just let us on the plane with it!&#x201D;&#xD;He then comes back after a short while, sword still in hand, and tells us to go and check the sword over in the baggage-check area or whatever. We gladly accept his advice without hesitation.&#xD;&#xD;Jokes of posters with my visage, stating &#x201C;Public Enemy #1&#x201D; being placed throughout every airport soon ensued, as well as my mom&#x2019;s realization that the man probably did not leave to see if we could bring the sword on the plane, but instead probably left to go see if he should detain all of us and press us for questioning of what we might know and then send us to Guantanamo.&#xD;&#xD;Needless to say, I shan&#x2019;t forget to check my bags now before getting onto a plane or any other national security nightmare. It was a &#x2026;fun experience to say the least, though.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
