<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>A journey through the life and times of Kevin Doyle</title>
    <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Old_Blog/Old_Blog.html</link>
    <description>Welcome to the magnificent place that is my blog. It is filled with wondrous stories of comedy, tragedy, wit, sarcasm, and totally nonsensical things!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please enjoy your stay.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Old_Blog/Old_Blog_files/Photo%20on%202010-06-11%20at%2017.52.jpg</url>
      <title>A journey through the life and times of Kevin Doyle</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Old_Blog/Old_Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Still Alive</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/9/30_Still_Alive.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16c83ea7-446b-4561-86d3-1177218b844d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 22:27:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>I still exist. I am just so very busy with school again, like I always am during the school year. Consider the school months my Hiatus time. I will be updating the other half of my site as well as this part more during breaks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is just a note to say I did not forget about you faithful readers (which is now probably 0 people.)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Anyone was Wondering</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/8/18_If_Anyone_was_Wondering.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01a0afa5-15a4-441d-9f99-b33785797b58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 00:08:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>The “Blog” link in the navibar is absent from the Science page on purpose. My intent was to not have the science page and the blog directly linked.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is like a literal navigation throughout the entirety of my site. You have to travel back to the main hub to go to the other section.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I will probably wind up posting a new science blog on the science page instead, like I said I was going to do, but haven’t gotten around to doing yet. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The two parts of the site are separate, but are linked by a lifelong bond regardless. They are siblings of the same birth yet perform vastly different purposes. If you do not like my decision here then too bad.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Also yes the comment box seems to have become beheaded. I would assume it is a problem with the code for it; I dunno. I’ll fix it somehow eventually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Rescued A Bird!</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/5/31_We_Rescued_A_Bird%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e2d6bca-aed5-4c2a-aff0-d0be6ace6d05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 17:27:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/5/31_We_Rescued_A_Bird%21_files/Screen%20shot%202012-05-31%20at%205.51.07%20PM.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Media/object012_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:254px; height:135px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Today, The Doyle Family has saved a life.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We were eating breakfast out on our deck when my dad noticed some ripples in the pool. Thinking it may have been a bird sitting in the pool, bathing or something of the sort, we went to check it out. Much to our surprise, it was a small baby bird who was gasping for air and struggling to stay alive. (He seemed to be doing a pretty good job of keeping his head above water too). My dad then got the pool skimmer and scooped the little fella out of the water and placed him on the grass. He sat there for a while and dried off a bit before we decided to place him in a shoebox with some newspaper bedding. He seemed pretty tired from swimming for his life, as most animals would, so we let him rest in the box for a bit before returning him to the wild. We read that most fledglings are actually meant to be semi-independent and hop around on the ground to forage for their own food while the parents occasionally come to assist. I felt like I should have known this, being the biology-minded one in my family…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Regardless, once it was time, we put the bird back underneath the bush in the shade near where he had fallen in the pool. Later in the day, my mom had gone back out to check on him and found that he wasn’t there anymore and had presumably gone inside the bush where she heard many bird chirping.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It’s a scary thought, though, that if we were not outside at that exact time, the fate of this bird would have been much different! Maybe one of those pool alarms that let you know if anything falls in would be useful after all…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/5/31_We_Rescued_A_Bird%21_files/Screen%20shot%202012-05-31%20at%205.51.07%20PM.jpg" length="59692" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site Modifications Complete!</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/5/20_Site_Modifications_Complete%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ba7ca0-c65c-45d6-a49f-318fed2c8b89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 23:55:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>The new section of my site is finished! As you might have noticed, there is now a homepage to my site which has links to access this blog as well as the new science section where I will be describing my current projects and the like! You can quick–access this new section through the URL science.mylifeisdoyle.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This site is finally being expanded after three years! Hooray! Be on the lookout for when I finally get around to writing about all my scientific undertakings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Plans</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/3/31_Future_Plans.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc667f13-06ae-4be5-8f01-513ec76dc21f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2012 16:46:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Recently I’ve been having some ideas about plans for my site. Seeing as I’m getting more involved with research at school and that I am even now in the beginning steps of starting my own experiment, I am going to make a whole new section to my site that will contain all the details of my scientific endeavors! Now I’ll finally have something that can mostly stand alone by itself without needing to be updated all the time (not that I update this blog too often anyway). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Expect these new exciting changes to be occurring within the next few months, seeing as I am still lazy when it comes to messing around with this stuff and I am also not too sure how to properly set this up which means I will be needing some outside assistance from a very well-established computer-man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things “R” Good</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2012/1/24_Things_R_Good.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6324a12d-93a2-43b1-abac-9778bff4a40e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 23:46:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>I have come to realize over this past year how lucky I really am. I went from totally miserable to the happiest I’ve ever been, and that would never have happened if all those Series of Unfortunate Events never took place! For instance, i.e., e.g., i.e.g., if my school did not get shut down by The Man, I would have never gone to Stony Brook’s wonderful Main Campus and subsequently joined their wind ensemble and then started talking to Nicole! We oftentimes discuss alternate timeline whereupon Southampton did not close and she decided to pursue her interest in the environmental sciences and then she would have went there too but like we might not have even really talked in that case and like aahjsaghdgsahjdhsajk! The thought is frightening. But she tells me, and I quote* “yeah, fuck the sciences; teaching little childrens is much more rewarding. LOL” &lt;br/&gt;        Regardless of this fact, we have been doing quite well! It’s nigh on one year now that we’ve been together, and what a year it was. Most peeps should have at least had some form of tiffs or quarrels between them in a year but we haven’t! We can’t find anything to get mad at each other over! Of course now you all will be all JUMPING UP on good ol’ Murphy’s Law here and say “LOL NOW YOU WILL THAT YOU’VE SAID THAT” but no, even Murphy cannot influence things—not even normal life occurrences, and this all has to do with my Thesis of “my girlfriend is always right.” She had self-designated this thesis to me, and after some observations, I have some data that proves this. FOR EXAMPLE: we went to eat at a restaurant and gave our name for the wait. We then went out to Walk on the Town for like, a time, and me being me was all “GOMGMO what if they call our name while we’re not in there?!?!?!?!” and she’s all “THEY WON’T; IT’S FINE.” and turns out we did not miss our seat-calling. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But I digress. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;        Our one-year anniversary together is coming up in February which is, of course, when school’s in session! The current plan is to take the intrepid journey up to the frost forsaken land of Potsdam, where temperatures delve so cold it makes even the Kelvin scale cry, so I can be there at least sometime during that month. I fear I might not survive the journey up there, though; having to scale the frozen peaks of the Adirondacks. Poor Stella most likely won’t be able to brave this trip, so I will have to take The Mountaineer, whose name oddly fits with the terrain that I’ll be driving across. As it seems currently, we look good for hopefully many more years into the future! I think I can say with confidence that this is the happiest I have been in a while, if not ever.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*note: quote is not verbatim&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I have also obtained yet another new Music Artist-Group who is quite splendid as well. They are… &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Weepies. &lt;br/&gt;Holy fuck. Yeah. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;        Sarah, who you all read about way back in my story about my lost sweatshirt, had posted a cryptic message on my Facebook Wall Timeline that read “Yo bro, listen to the weepies!” At the time, I had no idea what these “weepies” were. I thought they might have been some otherworldly entity that she was suggesting I take advice from. For what reasons I needed this advice I did not know. I disregarded these words for a while before I decided to take action and call her out on this mysterious phrase. Right after I did this, I had the bright idea to just search the term “the weepies” online and, lo and behold, I found out they were a band. I felt very foolish as the rest of that conversation with Sarah unfolded.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;        In time I came to possess their two most recent albums. After countless listen-throughs, I can state that they are like REALLY GOOD OH MY GOD. Their melodies are so fresh and so pure they warm my soul. Maybe I’ll do another “Kevin Listens To” of their music. I haven’t done one of those since October of 2010! …Holy shit, it’s been that long?! I really don’t post things too often here! But I guess that was always the way I wanted this thing to work: occasional posts with a decent amount of words in them that were pleasant to read! I did not want it to be like the infernal Tumblr: the bane of my entire blogging existence.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;        So yeah. I finish up this shorter-than-I-wanted-it-to-be-for-a-3-almost-4-month hiatus as I sit here at my school desk, all too ready to start yet another wonderful semester here at SBU. Two days in and it doesn’t seem so bad …yet. We’ll see though. Hopefully I will actually write things more often! LOL.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey Look, An Update!</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2011/10/1_Hey_Look,_An_Update%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c19fa81-687b-413c-ab01-7e3f31895555</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 1 Oct 2011 23:16:54 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Sup my broskis! Man, it’s been a while since I’ve been able to write anything here… And yes, I do mean able. I’ve been exceptionally busy since school’s started up again! Also no new hilarious antics have happened to inspire any sort of story writing. School is starting to become “for the serious,” as I believe I’ve mentioned in my last post or something; and also everyone of us is almost all gone (and by “us” I mean us Southamptoners). Next year it will only be my grade-year left; everyone else will have moved on… It will be so sad; no one will be left to carry on our legacy…&lt;br/&gt;    Semicolons aside, the School Front is going quite well this semester (for once). Have I mentioned the research work I’ve been doing at school? If not, I am now. I’m working under my professor in one of the labs here on the lovely hallowed grounds of Stony Brook. She, in turn, is working under the head lab PI Dr. Steven Baines. Maybe you’ve heard of him (you probably haven’t). There’s even a website for this lab, and we all have our pictures on it! Or at least we will; it’s still a work in-progress. For any who are interested, &lt;a href=&quot;http://life.bio.sunysb.edu/ee/baineslab/&quot;&gt;here’s the link&lt;/a&gt;. It’s so exciting; I’m on the Internet! I’m famous! …Oh wait.&lt;br/&gt;    Coinciding with the work I’ve been doing, I’ve been thinking about future plans for this site. Maybe one day I’ll also add a section with any science-endeavors I’m participating in and/or am pursuing. This would add more breadth to the site and henceforth increase its monetary value at least 10 fold!!! …Not that I really give all to big of a flying crap about that. But yes, I can also say I’ve been thinking about the future on a big-picture scale as well. I mean, undergraduate-funtimes are almost over! The Working World is waiting right around the corner! (As well as a fuckton more of schooling, since I am planning on going All The Way. Dr. Doyle, anybody? Fyea.) I’ve been thinking about how things will play out when it’s time to go for my graduate degree. Possibly getting an apartment somewhere… Going to school while working… Good stuff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But all this has to be taken one step at a time, as the cliché saying goes, and I can say I’m looking quite forward to it all as well. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
