<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab Journal</title>
    <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>Here, I will be documenting events that occur during my research exploits.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Projects:&lt;br/&gt;Acartia tonsa Fe limitation</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Blog_files/diatoms.jpg</url>
      <title>Lab Journal</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:subtitle>Here, I will be documenting events that occur during my research exploits.&#13;&#13;Projects:&#13;Acartia tonsa Fe limitation</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>Here, I will be documenting events that occur during my research exploits.&#13;&#13;Projects:&#13;Acartia tonsa Fe limitation</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:image href="http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Blog_files/diatoms.jpg"/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>On Culturing Iron Limited Phytoplankton&#13;</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2013/9/5_On_Culturing_Iron_Limited_Phytoplankton.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90296193-03ac-4b53-beeb-d6ad2d869130</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 Sep 2013 07:55:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>In order to grow T. oceanica at different iron concentrations, I need to strip all metals from the media they’ll be growing in before I can add my own. This is where a chelating compound, in the form of Chelex 100 Resin, comes in handy. Chelex is a highly purified chelating compound composed of styrene divinylbenzene copolymers which have iminodiacetate ions strewn within which act as the chelating molecules that bind metal ions and thus remove them from whatever media you pass through them. Technical description aside, it’s mostly a bunch of organic molecules with chelating molecules amongst them. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Chelex, however, must sit through a week-long cleaning process before it can actually be used. Sparing the details, it basically sits in methanol for a few hours then in 1 molar HCL overnight and then into 3 molar NH3OH for an entire week. The NH3OH is some pretty pungent stuff too. Getting a whiff of that will certainly clear out your sinuses. After that’s all done you need to suspend the Chelex in whatever media you plan to use it for and titrate it to pH 8.1—the pH of seawater. This is also a long process, as the Chelex is very good at buffering the media, which means it takes a good deal of NaOH to stabilize it to the correct pH.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The first time I made a Chelex column, the media I used was water from Stony Brook Harbor. I thought the column would remove the iron from this water and I’d be good to go to use it to grow my iron-cultures. I was definitely right, but so wrong at the same time. Only after a few passes through the column did I notice a dark brown spot forming in the top layer of the Chelex. I began to worry that the column was becoming saturated too quickly and would be useless. Not to mention my iron limited culture at the time did not seem very iron limited.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thinking I could recharge the Chelex, I soaked it in 1 molar HCL again overnight to, in theory, remove all the metal that was bound in there. I thought I’d see the Chelex change to a lighter shade after this, and I’m pretty sure I deluded myself into thinking I saw a change just to believe it worked. Eventually I tried this process again and instead used water from farther out at sea because the harbor water most likely contained far too much metal insomuch that the effluent still had significant amounts of iron in it (which would explain why the first cultures didn’t seem iron limited).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Using this open ocean water helped a little bit, as I did notice a slight difference in growth rate between the high and low iron cultures, but it still wasn’t as pronounced as it should have been. Desperate, I decided to try growing them in the artificial medium Aquil, which is DI water with different hydrous and anhydrous salts dissolved in it. Now I noticed a larger difference in growth rates, but it STILL wasn’t as different as it should be. I was still using that first Chelex column that I still pretended was clean enough to use. It was suggested that I make a new column and I thought this was a very good idea, and now using the comparison picture it is clear that the new one is much cleaner than the old one.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I recently made new cultures using the media passed through the new column and hopefully the differences between the cultures is even more pronounced this time.</description>
      <itunes:block>yes</itunes:block>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Creature in Copepod Culture</title>
      <link>http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Entries/2013/7/17_Mysterious_Creature_in_Copepod_Culture.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9be316-add6-40a3-bc4f-fd4355f2355e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 11:35:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Media/2013-07-05%2011.15.24.mov&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Blog/Media/2013-07-05%2011.15.24.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:339px; height:191px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;This is finally my first post regarding the things I do in the lab! As you may or may not know, I’ve been trying to keep a culture of the copepod Acartia tonsa alive for approximately two years now—and was successful… until spring break of last spring semester where I discovered that all of my four culture containers had died completley. I had no time to try and make a new culture as it was nearing Finals Week and I could hardly be in the lab at all.&lt;br/&gt;Once I started working in the lab again over the summer, I procured more copepods and started a new culture. I had forgotten how difficult it was to separate this species from every other possible creature in the catch water. Luckily, I devised a pretty good method for doing so this time: I filtered the entire catch through a filter column which first had a 1 mm size mesh and then had a 500 µm mesh expertly rigged to its bottom. This was most useful in separating the horrible crab larvae that can so easily slip past your eye and then wind up eating all the copepods you’ve transferred.&lt;br/&gt;A few days after I set up these new filtered cultures containing (mostly) Acartia tonsa, I noticed this odd thing stuck on the bottom of one of the containers that was flailing around what I assume to be some sort of feeding apparatus. At first I thought it was cute—most likely posing no harm other than eating some of the algae I’d feed the copepods with— and I’d leave it there until the next time I’d filter the copepods into new water, but later on I saw about four of them attached to the bottom and side of a second container. Coinciding with this observation, I noticed that there had not been many new nauplii swimming around in these cultures. Maybe it was possible these things were eating the small nauplii as well as any algae in there? I then urgently filtered out the copepods to put into another container. As it turns out, though, most of the copepods in these cultures weren’t even the correct species, as they had egg sacks attached and Acartia tonsa is a sans-egg sack species. Some copepods from a third container I had seemed to be correct, so I isolated them and now they’ve successfully begot enough copepods to create a whole new culture of the correct species.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now once I get the diatom I’m using for the this project, Thalassiosira oceanica, iron limited I can finally start the actual experiment…</description>
      <enclosure url="http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Media/2013-07-05%2011.15.24.mov" length="28447072" type="video/quicktime"/>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>00:00:21</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:subtitle>This is finally my first post regarding the things I do in the lab! As you may or may not know, I’ve been trying to keep a culture of the copepod Acartia tonsa alive for approximately two years now—and was successful… until spring bre</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>This is finally my first post regarding the things I do in the lab! As you may or may not know, I’ve been trying to keep a culture of the copepod Acartia tonsa alive for approximately two years now—and was successful… until spring break of last spring semester where I discovered that all of my four culture containers had died completley. I had no time to try and make a new culture as it was nearing Finals Week and I could hardly be in the lab at all.&#13;Once I started working in the lab again over the summer, I procured more copepods and started a new culture. I had forgotten how difficult it was to separate this species from every other possible creature in the catch water. Luckily, I devised a pretty good method for doing so this time: I filtered the entire catch through a filter column which first had a 1 mm size mesh and then had a 500 µm mesh expertly rigged to its bottom. This was most useful in separating the horrible crab larvae that can so easily slip past your eye and then wind up eating all the copepods you’ve transferred.&#13;A few days after I set up these new filtered cultures containing (mostly) Acartia tonsa, I noticed this odd thing stuck on the bottom of one of the containers that was flailing around what I assume to be some sort of feeding apparatus. At first I thought it was cute—most likely posing no harm other than eating some of the algae I’d feed the copepods with— and I’d leave it there until the next time I’d filter the copepods into new water, but later on I saw about four of them attached to the bottom and side of a second container. Coinciding with this observation, I noticed that there had not been many new nauplii swimming around in these cultures. Maybe it was possible these things were eating the small nauplii as well as any algae in there? I then urgently filtered out the copepods to put into another container. As it turns out, though, most of the copepods in these cultures weren’t even the correct species, as they had egg sacks attached and Acartia tonsa is a sans-egg sack species. Some copepods from a third container I had seemed to be correct, so I isolated them and now they’ve successfully begot enough copepods to create a whole new culture of the correct species.&#13;&#13;Now once I get the diatom I’m using for the this project, Thalassiosira oceanica, iron limited I can finally start the actual experiment…</itunes:summary>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
