<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="E599D35C-4A5A-4890-B321-34A532B526B9">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20130723" date="2013-07-23 10:29:28 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Mysterious Creature in Copepod Culture</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>7/17/13</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>This is finally my first post regarding the things I do in the lab! As you may or may not know, I&#x2019;ve been trying to keep a culture of the copepod &lt;i&gt;Acartia tonsa &lt;/i&gt;alive for approximately two years now&#x2014;and was successful&#x2026; until spring break of last spring semester where I discovered that all of my four culture containers had died completley. I had no time to try and make a new culture as it was nearing Finals Week and I could hardly be in the lab at all.&#xD;Once I started working in the lab again over the summer, I procured more copepods and started a new culture. I had forgotten how difficult it was to separate this species from every other possible creature in the catch water. Luckily, I devised a pretty good method for doing so this time: I filtered the entire catch through a filter column which first had a 1 mm size mesh and then had a 500 &#xB5;m mesh expertly rigged to its bottom. This was most useful in separating the horrible crab larvae that can so easily slip past your eye and then wind up eating all the copepods you&#x2019;ve transferred.&#xD;A few days after I set up these new filtered cultures containing (mostly) &lt;i&gt;Acartia tonsa, &lt;/i&gt;I noticed this odd thing stuck on the bottom of one of the containers that was flailing around what I assume to be some sort of feeding apparatus. At first I thought it was cute&#x2014;most likely posing no harm other than eating some of the algae I&#x2019;d feed the copepods with&#x2014; and I&#x2019;d leave it there until the next time I&#x2019;d filter the copepods into new water, but later on I saw about four of them attached to the bottom and side of a second container. Coinciding with this observation, I noticed that there had not been many new nauplii swimming around in these cultures. Maybe it was possible these things were eating the small nauplii as well as any algae in there? I then urgently filtered out the copepods to put into another container. As it turns out, though, most of the copepods in these cultures weren&#x2019;t even the correct species, as they had egg sacks attached and &lt;i&gt;Acartia tonsa &lt;/i&gt;is a sans-egg sack species. Some copepods from a third container I had seemed to be correct, so I isolated them and now they&#x2019;ve successfully begot enough copepods to create a whole new culture of the correct species.&#xD;&#xD;Now once I get the diatom I&#x2019;m using for the this project, &lt;i&gt;Thalassiosira oceanica&lt;/i&gt;, iron limited I can finally start the actual experiment&#x2026;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
