<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:10 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Summer Reflection</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;August 5, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>        So it&#x2019;s almost that time again&#x2014;the end of summer&#x2026; or at least it feels like it. It feels like it just started too. It&#x2019;s almost my birthday and I, honestly, completely forgot it was coming up on the horizon. It feels like it should still be months away. Surprisingly though, I don&#x2019;t mind that summer&#x2019;s almost over; even though I&#x2019;ve been quite busy as of late and haven&#x2019;t had time to do &#x201C;summer things.&#x201D; Part of this might be me coming to terms with the fact that summers basically do just stop happening once you find yourself immersed in the real world and real world responsibilities. But yes, I&#x2019;m actually looking forward to the fall. Not just for school to start again, but for the season itself. I&#x2019;ve always had this affinity towards the fall season, but for some reason I&#x2019;m looking forward to it even more so this year and I can&#x2019;t say why exactly. I just really want to feel the &lt;i&gt;cool crisp air&lt;/i&gt; and see the &lt;i&gt;orange and brown foliage&lt;/i&gt; and, of course, &lt;i&gt;wear my sweatshirt again&lt;/i&gt; even more than usual. I really can&#x2019;t wait to be able to just meander down one of the many paths on campus and take in what the season has to offer. It will also be nice to see everyone again, of course. Some people have left and gone to do bigger and more important things with their lives, though, so it will be sad to see them gone&#x2026; Many people have also left to go live in the &lt;i&gt;apartments&lt;/i&gt; instead, which means they&#x2019;re basically gone forever. We&#x2019;re never going to see them again. Luckily the Dynamic Duo Trio is still together! Marc, Kenny, and I will hold strong to keep the three newbs in our suite in line &#x2026;if it comes to that. And of course we&#x2019;ll have more crazy antics up our sleeves too. I, personally, await with bated breath to see the interactions between Marc and Kenny again. Will Marc finally get around to giving Kenny his comeuppance? Who knows.&#xD;        I also have a feeling this semester is going to feel vastly different from previous ones for whatever reason. Like, sort of in the sense that &#x201C;shit just got real&#x201D; now. Actual goals are on the horizon, and now&#x2019;s the time to get one&#x2019;s foot out there in The World. On a related note, I still can&#x2019;t believe this will already be my junior year. It seriously still feels like I was a freshman just last semester. So much has happened in these few short years since I&#x2019;ve started school that you&#x2019;d think it should feel like a good amount of time has passed since then&#x2026; I&#x2019;m not sure why all of this is going so fast. It still feels like I just met all my friends from school! I&#x2019;m not too worried about staying in touch since in today&#x2019;s world we have miraculous technology like &lt;i&gt;Facebook&lt;/i&gt;, and now the most highly anticipated new social networking system: &lt;i&gt;Google+&lt;/i&gt;. Despite that, the fact that we&#x2019;re all almost done with the one medium that brought us all together still feels weird.&#xD;&#xD; &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;         Well, I think I&#x2019;ve reflected on this existential exploration enough now. It seems like you never know what kinds of things I&#x2019;ll post next, and that&#x2019;s why this blog-site is the best one ever! There is just so much diversity that it is not even funny. &#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;I will stop being narcissistic now and bid you all farewell.&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
