<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 22:59:54 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText></richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>An Emotional Vociferation</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Just call me Irony Man. Tragic fucking Irony Man. I seem to be oh so good at giving advice to others helping them with &lt;i&gt;their &lt;/i&gt;relationships, and yet, I continue to screw myself over time after time, (and here&#x2019;s the best part) following my own advice.&#xD;&#xD;God damn it. What the hell am I supposed to do now, move on and find someone else? No, that just will not work, I&#x2019;m sorry. I&#x2019;ll never feel the same way about anybody else I&#x2019;ll find. I&#x2019;m going to see anyone else, essentially, as a replacement; which will just fuck with everything the way it is now. I am not going to be able to feel one way about someone, and another slightly different way about someone else. To me, that seems weirder than having both feelings for one single person. I find the latter to be the best possible situation actually, but unfortunately this usually doesn&#x2019;t happen to most people; the reason being is that most people are just never able to find that one single amazing person in their lives who means everything to them. So, again fitting with this rant&#x2019;s theme, how ironic is it that I have the potential for this situation to work, and yet it fails for a completely different reason? (One that I&#x2019;d even say can be resolved, but who knows; I may just be screwing myself over for still hoping things change in the future). I&#x2019;d say plenty, but I&#x2019;m not sure if I used the term &#x201C;irony&#x201D; correctly here. Please excuse me, I cannot think very well about the usage of rhetorical devices at the moment.&#xD;&#xD;So, in short, I have no idea what to do anymore. I emotionally unable to move on, seeing as I don&#x2019;t differentiate between the two different ways I&#x2019;m &#x201C;supposed&#x201D; to feel. And in any potential future relationships, I&#x2019;m always going to want to start off as friends with someone before anything else happens, but apparently I&#x2019;m alone in feeling this way. So unless I&#x2019;m able to pull some God forsaken miracle out of my ass, I think I&#x2019;ll be screwed for life.&#xD;&#xD;Alas, such are the trials and tribulations of Irony Man.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;Or maybe I&#x2019;m wrong about all of this. I don&#x2019;t know. It&#x2019;s a lot to think about.&#xD;&#xD;And now reflecting upon it all, I feel very &#x2026;empty. Or &#x2026;hollow &#x2026;inside.&#xD;I almost feel like crying, but &#x2026;I can&#x2019;t.&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;Y&#x2019;know what, all I&#x2019;m ever going to be good for is a friend. I give up. I should just learn to accept it.&#xD;Ugh. I really hate now having to pretend to be happy for everyone.&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;Reflecting back, I&#x2019;m ok now. I just have to see where this goes in time&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;March 21, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
