<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:00 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>And the plot thickens!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 10, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>So yesterday, I was hanging out in my room getting kind of hungry when Marc (he is my roommate in case you did not know. Which you didn&#x2019;t) waltz in. I seize this as an opportunity to go across the street and get some food. Once we arrive, we then stand on the burger line for &#x2248;40 minutes until we obtain our food. There weren&#x2019;t even that many people on the line to begin with; they were just REALLY SLOW. But I can empathize with them, seeing as I once held the same type of horrendous job. &#x2026;But I digress. After I had gotten my food, I go over to the soda fountain, to no surprise, to get a drink. There was this one girl there getting her beverage before me, and I had reached for my 16 ounce paper cup when she and I started giggling due to the obvious lack of space we both had standing there. So after I had gotten my drink, I went to go pay for my meal. As it turns out, she is already right in front of me on line. She notices; giggles again, and then picks up a bag of Funyuns&#xAE;. I was totally baffled; I love those things! Seeing that a girl would enjoy overly garlicky-oniony empowered snacks, I became intrigued. However, she then left the food-purchasing room to what I could only think was the dining area. After I purchased my food, I waited for Marc to finish his food related shenanigans and then we went to go sit down. Hoping she was still in here &lt;i&gt;somewhere, &lt;/i&gt;I perused the first area only to see that she wasn&#x2019;t there. I was a tad bit defeated, but I had not given up hope yet! Sure enough, there she was in the back area: sitting by herself on one of those individual table type deals. Seeing as Marc was with me, and being the slightly socially awkward person I am: I did not sit with her. Instead, we sat down next to/across from the table she was at. I glanced over now and then to get a better look at her. She was indeed fairly attractive, and I was hoping she was looking at me too. Later on, I heard some beautiful sounds emanating from somewhere in the room. I then realize that she is in fact SINGING! Oh man, she sang too! She&#x2019;s a music-type person! This all seemed too good to be true. &#xD;&#xD;Sure enough, Marc and I finish eating first and leave. I glanced over to her as we were leaving, but she was not looking. I&#x2019;m really not sure why I didn&#x2019;t say anything to her at all: e.g., &#x201C;oh man, you like Funyuns&#xAE; too? That&#x2019;s to crazy!&#x201D; But, alas, I did not. &#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;m going to refer to this girl as Mystery Girl from now on. I really do hope I&#x2019;ll be able to find her again eventually. Sooner than later is preferred. I&#x2019;ll have to get all of my friends to help me on this, using only the description of &#x201C;she&#x2019;s got brown hair, is about my height, likes Funyuns&#xAE; and sings&#x201D; to find her. &#xD;&#xD;This should be fun.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
