<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:00 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The Enthralling Journey</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 12, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Earlier today, I experienced an awful tragedy. It was something so horribly unfathomable you have no idea: &#xD;&#xD;I had lost&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;My Sweatshirt.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;It was time for me to do my laundry today, as I plan on doing it every Sunday to stick to a routine clothes-washing-regime. I went into my closet to grab my hamper when I notice something about my closet isn&#x2019;t quite right; something seems to be missing&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;And then it hits me: my Sweatshirt is gone.&#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;m completely baffled; I can&#x2019;t even remember the last time I wore it. I kept asking myself: &#x201C;where could it be?! I &lt;i&gt;couldn&#x2019;t &lt;/i&gt;have absentmindedly left it in some building around campus. If I had, it&#x2019;d be long gone by now. I &lt;i&gt;did &lt;/i&gt;need a new sweatshirt anyway, but I didn&#x2019;t want my current Sweatshirt to go out like this&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;I call upon the aid of Kenny: one of my suite mates, as we were both about to go do laundry together. He tries to give me ideas of where I could have left it, when it hits me: I was wearing it the other day when Sarah (yet another friend from school) and I went to go find the pool! (Which, by the way, we failed at doing.) I remembered constantly pulling my sleeves up due to the drastic temperature changes between the buildings and the outside world. I contacted her, asking if I had left it in her suite, while I put my laundry in the wash.&#xD;&#xD;I awaited her response with bated breath.&#xD;&#xD;Finally, she responded with &#x201C;you mean the Old Navy one?&#x201D;&#xD;&#xD;I was elated; I thought she had it! Why else would she refer to it as &#x201C;the &lt;i&gt;Old Navy one&lt;/i&gt;&#x201D; without actually having it?&#xD;&#xD;Alas, she didn&#x2019;t have it. I sunk way back into Sweatshirt Depression. I seriously could not, for the life of me, think of where it could be? I continued to press her for answers. I had originally thought that after our (lack of) pool shenanigans we had went back up to her room, but she had clarified that we had, in fact, not done so. Her ankle hurt, so we instead retired to each other&#x2019;s respective rooms. &#xD;&#xD;The case was reopened. I tried to think of anywhere else it could have been. It was quite a challenging task. I took a guess and thought it may have been in my &lt;i&gt;other &lt;/i&gt;friends&#x2019; (consisting of a variety of females that I may have need to mention in detail sometime in the future) suite.&#xD;&#xD;After putting my laundry (sans Sweatshirt) in the washer, I dashed up to the aforementioned friends&#x2019; suite, only to find that the friend whose room it may have been in wasn&#x2019;t there at the moment. &lt;i&gt;&#x201C;I was shocked, but not surprised.&#x201D; &#x2013;&#x2013;Roy Grey, Monochromatic 36&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;That quote really doesn&#x2019;t fit too well here. Rather: I was disappointed, but not downfallen. I could only think of &lt;i&gt;one &lt;/i&gt;other place it &lt;i&gt;may &lt;/i&gt;have been in: my other friend Sara&#x2019;s suite (yes, another &#x201C;Sarah&#x201D; [minus the H]. I know like &lt;i&gt;so many &lt;/i&gt;&#x201C;Sarah&#x201D;s now, and I knew exactly zero (0) before college.)&#xD;&#xD;I then give it one last shot and go and check to see if my Sweatshirt is in Sara&#x2019;s suite for whatever reason. (I could not actually think of any reason for why it would be in there.)&#xD;&#xD;I arrive at her suite door, which I then knock upon vigorously. One of her suite mates answers and leads me to Sara&#x2019;s room. My roommate Marc is also present.&#xD;&#xD;I begin to walk in, asking &#x201C;would you fellows happen to know if you&#x2019;ve seen my&#x2013;&#x2013;&#x201D;&#xD;&#xD;and there it is: &#xD;&#xD;My Sweatshirt!&#xD;&#xD;It was laying on the back of Sara&#x2019;s roommate&#x2019;s chair! Apparently I had left it in there when we had taken a trip to Petco the other day. WHY COULD I NOT REMEMBER THIS BEFORE?! But that was besides the point; the main thing was that my Sweatshirt and I were reunited at last. I was so happy you have no idea. I&#x2019;m always SO CAREFUL and PARANOID about misplacing things, and of course I then lose the one thing I would never hope to lose.&#xD;&#xD;But all is well now. I have learned to be more attentive about where I leave my Sweatshirt from now on.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
