<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:01 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>MAJOR SUCCESS!!!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 14, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Latest update (to this entry): 9/19/10&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;OH MY FG IT WORKED! THE ULCER-INDUCING SETTING UP ON THE &lt;i&gt;A.N. HOSTING &lt;/i&gt;SERVER I BOUGHT THE DOMAIN NAME FROM WORKED! &lt;b&gt;Edit: (yeah, I wound up not buying from &#x201C;&#x201D;&#x201D;GoDaddy&#x201D;&#x201D;&#x201D; because Ricky showed me one of the VlogBros. videos about buying from A.N. Hosting and I was all &#x201C;k.&#x201D; Cause apparently they had FTP server capabilities. And I really didn&#x2019;t want to have to subscribe to MobileMe just to post my site using my own domain).&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;I AM SO EXCITED OMG.&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;So yeah, now you all have to go to &#xD;&#xD;&lt;a href="http://www.MyLifeisDoyle.com"&gt;www.MyLifeisDoyle.com&lt;/a&gt; &#xD;&#xD;to see my site!&#xD;&#xD;(Credits go to Andrew Lo for pretty much coming up with that title and I just adored it so much).&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;9/15/10 Update:&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I think I&#x2019;m going to remove the Facebook notification for when I update here. I still want this blog to feel &lt;i&gt;somewhat &lt;/i&gt;of a secret/private place, even though I &lt;i&gt;do &lt;/i&gt;know people read it. At least it will give the &lt;i&gt;allusion &lt;/i&gt;that it&#x2019;s all private/secret.&#xD;&#xD;I use italics too much.&#xD;&#xD;Also omfmogmofg I can now publish music here again without any errors which meant nothing but were annoying nonetheless!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Expect great things in the future.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;Update:&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;And now I&#x2019;m having Fun with Fonts! The main title of the site now looks better than before. &#xD;I am so Giddy with Glee &#x2026;and alliteration.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;9/19/10 Update (Again!):&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;So it has come to my attention that most computers do not have the font for the title of this here blog! I &lt;i&gt;got by with a little help from my friends &lt;/i&gt;and used the advice of taking a picture of the title and then placing that over the font. GENIUS!&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;Why can I never think of simple things like this.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
