<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:01 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>303: The Musical</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 26, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Alright, I feel I should finally be posting an update regarding the newest updates to my life. The topic of this post will be all over the place (i.e., SO MANY TOPICS) so it will be so much fun to read. Yay!&#xD;&#xD;I am so very close to changing my major to the acclaimed Biology degree. The process to actually do this doesn&#x2019;t seem &lt;i&gt;too &lt;/i&gt;convoluted, but who knows. They could very well give me an extremely hard time about it (why they would deter students from &lt;i&gt;academically flourishing &lt;/i&gt;I have no idea) but I really hope they don&#x2019;t. If they do, I shall surely be &lt;a href="http://mylifeisdoyle.com/My_Life_is_Doyle/Home/Entries/2009/11/3_IMMA_FIRIN_MA_LAZOR!.html"&gt;firin&#x2018; ma lazor&lt;/a&gt; at them. In going through with this, I&#x2019;m going to have a hell of a time &#x201C;catching up,&#x201D; per say, on the classes I will now need to take for this major. Calc B, and every single Biology and Chemistry course known to mankind just to name a few. But I don&#x2019;t care; I&#x2019;m going to put myself through this and I&#x2019;m going to LIKE it, goddamnit!&#xD;&#xD;Getting into &lt;i&gt;dorm life,&lt;/i&gt; it has been determined that this semester has been deemed the &#x201C;musical semester.&#x201D; Yes, joyful singing and dancing about things that would not normally be sang and danced about all around! This all started from some cool peeps deciding to watch the musical episode of The Vampire Slayer that is Buffy. After that, I suggested we watch the most amazing romantic comedy/tragedy ever: Dr. Horrible&#x2018;s Sing Along Blog. We also then watched the commentary version (Commentary! The Musical) which prompted me to purchase the soundtrack of C!tM, which was just about the best purchasing decision I&#x2019;ve ever made (aside from buying this domain name, of course).&#xD;So yes, we then watched Repo! The Genetic Opera, which was quite interesting. I felt the storyline was very well crafted, all while focusing around a very abstract and bizarre plot-theme. &lt;/critic&gt;&#xD;And due to all these musical-happenings, our suite (suite 303) has decided this semester will be one whole musical, entitled 303: The Musical. It will be such a big hit; tickets go on sale possibly sometime in the near future. Keep a look out.&#xD;&#xD;Also musically related is the concept of the band that Marc and I are supposed to be creating. We&#x2026; haven&#x2019;t been all too productive with this. First off, we still do need a drummer, and a female drummer at that. (I have decided that the band should consist of three people: me on guitar/sax and vocals [LAWLS, ME SINGING], Marc on bass, and a drummer who is female for additional female vocals). However, &lt;i&gt;finding &lt;/i&gt;a female drummer is pretty much near impossible, despite the ever-so-large amount of people present here on campus; and when we &lt;i&gt;do &lt;/i&gt;find a drummer, we&#x2019;re going to have to actually become serious, and so far we can play a grand total of Zero (0) songs.&#xD;&#x2026;Maybe once I take guitar lessons over winter break we&#x2019;ll be able to get started on this.&#xD;&#xD;Oh, and I should say that I am giving up on that whole &#x201C;Mystery Girl&#x201D; deal. I really would even care if I did find her. I&#x2019;m just going to let things run their course and see how things play out in the long run. From time to time I still do think back to &#xD;&#x2026;the past&#x2026; and I get rather sad by it all, but I do get over it fairly quickly. Part of me still hopes things will get better, seeing as they apparently aren&#x2019;t even though I had the impression they were. &#x2026;I &lt;i&gt;am &lt;/i&gt;looking into how things will go with other person(s), though, so who knows. I really don&#x2019;t know what will happen, regarding everything as a whole.&#xD;&#x2026;I was probably smart to write this entry now when I&#x2019;m not in a sad/angry mood, otherwise I would have been all overly emotionally dramatic again, and I&#x2019;ve done that enough.&#xD;&#xD;To wrap things up, I should also mention that I &lt;b&gt;got a new sweatshirt.&lt;/b&gt; I know, I know: right after almost losing my precious signature sweatshirt I go and welcome a new one into my life? Well, yes. It &lt;i&gt;is &lt;/i&gt;rather comfy&#x2026; and now I can have two &#xD;sig-shirts! (That was a horrible portmanteau).&#xD;&#xD;Oh, and I also realized last night talking to Marc that I &lt;i&gt;do &lt;/i&gt;have some interesting stories that happened to me to write about on here! I&#x2019;m not totally boring like I thought I was compared to Allie&#x2019;s life at Hyperbole and a Half! &#xD;Expect this one (and maybe more once I think of them) story eventually.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
