<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:01 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Stress: The Breakfast of Anti-Champions</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 30, 2010 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; &#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I&#x2019;m feeling so very stressed out lately. Nothing seems to be cohesive right now. Mainly, I&#x2019;m troubled by the fact that 3/4th of the classes I&#x2019;m taking this semester are essentially pointless for when I change to Biology and how I &lt;b&gt;must &lt;/b&gt;excel in them, despite having no real motivation to do so, or else have my GPA forever desecrated to an horrible state of practically no return. It certainly doesn&#x2019;t help that one of these classes, economics no less, has been annoying me in the sense that I somehow keep doing things wrong even though I am doing what I &lt;i&gt;thought &lt;/i&gt;I learned in class. And now our first exam is coming up soon, so I shall soon see how doomed I am with respect to needing to begrudgingly struggle through this basically worthless semester.&#xD;&#xD;This physics class I&#x2019;m in is yet another class that could be potentially rubbing me the wrong way. For the most part, it &lt;i&gt;eh. &lt;/i&gt;(KC inserted that &#x201C;eh,&#x201D; which she insisted I keep, and I will because it does express my feelings towards the class). But no, it &lt;i&gt;could &lt;/i&gt;maybe count for a basic physics class later on, but I don&#x2019;t know that for sure. I guess if you want to take a positive approach regarding this all, this physics class is surely helping me realize that I really am not a fan of applied sciences. Y&#x2019;know, the ones with &lt;i&gt;math&lt;/i&gt;. I know even more now that I enjoy life sciences (e.g., Biology) much, &lt;b&gt;much &lt;/b&gt;better. &#xD;I can&#x2019;t get around to finally changing my major fast enough&#x2026; &#xD;This weekend. It must happen.&#xD;&#xD;I was also informed that you &lt;i&gt;can, &lt;/i&gt;in fact, repair your GPA eventually, but unfortunately, that&#x2019;s not how my mind works: I &lt;i&gt;can&#x2019;t &lt;/i&gt;do bad academically. I feel like an utter failure if I do, even if it doesn&#x2019;t affect my grade in the long run. That mark of failure will always be there; omnipresent, if you will, on my transcript. And then I&#x2019;ll just feel very bad because of that, possibly losing sleep at night and having to cry myself to sleep.&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;10/1/10 Update:&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;I guess another thing bothering me is that I feel&#x2026; lonely. Not in the sense that I don&#x2019;t acknowledge my friends-- because I do. You are all awesome. (And if you&#x2019;re not my friend, then you&#x2019;re still awesome because you&#x2019;re reading this and I don&#x2019;t even know who you are). It&#x2019;s just that I&#x2019;ve generally always had someone in my life that I regarded as an individual who I cared about in a different way than anyone else. Once that would end with someone, due to a various assortment of reasons, I&#x2019;d be able to get over it fairly quickly and be fine with it until I found someone else. But&#x2026; that isn&#x2019;t happening this time. It concerns me and, quite frankly, is a bit frustrating.&#xD;&#xD;My friend, Josh, actually just released a short film, somewhat pertaining to this. It&#x2019;s called Acceptance, and can be found on his site, &lt;a href="http://HzStudios.com/"&gt;HzStudios.com&lt;/a&gt;. He&#x2019;s a cooldude who also has his own domain name. He was also part of the motivation behind buying this domain. I thought &#x201C;if Josh can purchase his own domain, then so can I!!1!&#x201D;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;I figure I&#x2019;ve talked enough about me and my life now. The next entry will definitely be that amazing story that I talked about in a previous post &#x2026;which also has to do about my life, seeing that this &lt;i&gt;is &lt;/i&gt;the topic of my blog in the first place. So uh, yeah. More life-endeavor stories to come.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
