<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 22:59:59 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>New site theme!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 5, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>As you may have noticed, I just changed the theme of my blog. I was growing &lt;i&gt;tired&lt;/i&gt; of the dark, dismal &#x201C;darkroom&#x201D; layout that I had before. This layout makes my rather seemingly meaningless posts seem more &#x2026;professional. However, changing the theme wasn&#x2019;t as easy as I had hoped. I selected the new theme from the happy drop-down menu, whereupon the theme of the main page had then changed to fit my selected choice. It wasn&#x2019;t until I decided to check on my actual &lt;i&gt;entries &lt;/i&gt;when I saw the horror of my carefully planned out layout of the text boxes and other miscellaneous things had all been REARRANGED. I had fun moving things around in EVER ENTRY I&#x2019;VE EVER MADE. Now I know I&#x2019;ll be in for an even more exciting time if I ever want to change the theme again!&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;I&#x2019;ve used the word &#x201C;theme&#x201D; way too many times in that paragraph.&#xD;&#xD;On a different note, I also believe I am getting over The Topic that which made up most of the percentage of my last posts. &#xD;I might possibly be considering someone else now. She was a fellow Southampton student, but I guess I never thought about it then due to: 1) I was concerned with &#x2026;other things, and 2) she was taken. But, as it turns out, she was one of the many couples that ended in a horrible, flaming plane crash over the summer. Yes, crazy, I know; especially after my past huge rants about all of this. You may feel it appropriate to call me a &#x201C;whiny hypocrite&#x201D; or something of the sort, but OH WELL I don&#x2019;t care. I&#x2019;m going to have to see how this plays out, though. It seems somewhat promising; who knows.&#xD;&#xD;And as of today, I have been suffering from MAJOR ALLERGIES. I have been blowing my nose and/or sneezing ALL DAY. I best not be getting sick; I can&#x2019;t afford that now, not with school just starting!&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;Ah, yup; there I go sneezing again. &#xD;&#xD;    Fffffffuuuuuuuuu--&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
