<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:00 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>An extraordinary dream</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;September 8, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I just had the most amazing dream, and not necessarily in the good connotation of that word. It was about Southampton and what it could have been.&#xD;&#xD;For some reason, my family and I were out there on the campus visiting. It was before school was starting, and there were people everywhere. Everyone seemed so happy to be walking around associating; everyone knew each other, and I knew them as well.&#xD;There was a basketball hoop near what I think was Chancellor&#x2019;s Hall (why the aspect of basketball was in my dream, I&#x2019;ll never know), and someone I knew was shooting hoops. And then there was this girl, shooting hoops as well. She seemed to be a freshman; an incoming student to this upcoming year. One of her shots had rebounded and came over towards me where I then threw it back to her. She gladly accepted.&#xD;The actual area of the school where my dream took place--Chancellor&#x2019;s Hall--looked different too: it was partway intertwined with the outside (which was where the basketball hoop was). The main hallway opened up with a crossways section of an outside pathway, covered in brilliant green grass with an expansive bench towards the back whereupon I was sitting. I believe this bench was a rendition of the preexisting benches that sat parallel to the wall-sized windows that existed in the actual building. It seemed like a utopia of sorts.&#xD;This whole area, like I said, was filled with students. I also remember someone coming and sitting next to me, who I knew as well, and we chatted it up (for as much as I can remember, anyway; I don&#x2019;t really recall in-dream exchanges).&#xD;And then, just like that, I was bluntly thrust into the world by the alarming buzzer of my alarm.&#xD;&#xD;It was just all so nice. &#x2026;And sad as well. I remember the feeling of tears welling up as I thought about all of this and walked around and saw the school logo in various places.&#xD;&#xD;I guess some things just weren&#x2019;t meant to be.&#xD;&#xD;I seem to have a lot of that right now.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
