<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:08 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Observations</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;April 2, 2011&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>.&#xD;..&#xD;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;...&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;&#x2026;....&#xD;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#x2026;&#xD;SYSTEM REBOOT: &#xD;&#xD;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#x2014;&#xD;&#xD;&#x2026;Hello? Am&#x2026; am I&#x2026; &lt;i&gt;back? &lt;/i&gt;Oh man, I don&#x2019;t know how I survived the past&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;month&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt; I do think I&#x2019;ve realized a couple of things during my roughly-one-month-long absence. I&#x2019;ve mostly noticed the effects of prolonged stress on &lt;i&gt;certain individuals &lt;/i&gt;here at school. A certain individual, whose name will be omitted here for their protection, has totally gone of the deep end. He is no longer the happy, innocent, young strapping lad he once was back in Southampton. Now he has begun his slow decent into Demonhood. The torrential rage he secretly expresses towards other members of the populous is solely known by me. I am the only one who knows of his terrible plans of world domination and radical change. As an aside, I feel I should try to warn you all now because I know no one will believe me when the time comes. When this individual attempts to run for president, &lt;b&gt;do not vote for him.&lt;/b&gt; He will tempt you with his seemingly spectacular new ideas that he wishes to bestow upon you, but he has evil ulterior motives that will not make themselves known until it is too late! I know no one will heed my words (either because no one will believe me, or because approximately &#x2264; 0.0000000001&#x2030; of the worlds population actually knows about and reads this blog), but just remember that it was &lt;i&gt;me &lt;/i&gt;who tried to save you all.&#xD;&#xD;I&#x2019;ve also noticed my own slow degradation as well. As you know from the last post from eons ago, this semester has been my favorite. Throughout the many weeks henceforth, I&#x2019;ve began to see the corruption hidden beneath the surface. The classes are taught with such apathy towards having you truly understand the material that it makes me sick. The system is designed to destroy the hopes and dreams of some and have only the &lt;i&gt;elite few &lt;/i&gt;succeed. Granted, this may simply due to the massive size of classes and how it is an unfeasible task to be able to provide such tender love and care to each student as if they were the precious children whose eventual dreams and ambitions are to be handed to them on a silver platter. But if this be the case, then I again feel The System should be changed! Alas, I think it is too late for society to change. People must suffer to hope to succeed in school and then laugh at those who must endure the same fate they did once in the past.&#xD;&#xD;Regardless, this stress from attempting to survive as well as the Rage that manifested itself after realizing what I previously stated has taken its tole on me. I have become, as some say, &lt;i&gt;grimdark.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mspaintadventures.com/?s=6&amp;p=005595"&gt;This&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; is probably what I look like sometimes when I am heading to class or something. I&#x2019;ve also noticed that my expletive use has become &lt;i&gt;much &lt;/i&gt;less restrained as well. Sometimes I&#x2019;ll go off on a hilarious swearing spree, even when the situation doesn&#x2019;t really call for it!&#xD;Now that the semester is almost over, however, I am feeling a bit better. The omnipresent feeling of crushing despair has somewhat lifted, only to most likely present itself again once it&#x2019;s exam time again and the possibility of failure rears its head again. But for the time being, I will try to keep my sanity and enjoy the nicer things in life, because they &lt;i&gt;do &lt;/i&gt;exist even though I have made it seem like they do not. I&#x2019;ll also, again, na&#xEF;vely think and hope that next semester will be better, so we&#x2019;ll see how things go from here!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
