<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:03 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Updates. They happen sometimes.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;November 16, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Hello there, everybody. I just realized haven&#x2019;t really &lt;i&gt;updated&lt;/i&gt;, per say, recently. Nothing really all too exciting has happened lately, so I guess that&#x2019;d be a good reason behind this. Our band concert is soon though, that&#x2019;s something. And I had the honor of listening to the ornate orchestra that Nicole&#x2019;s a member of the other night on the very same stage whereupon we will having our band performance on Thursday, November Eighteenth at Eight O&#x2019;Clock Post Meridian with ticket prices being Five (5) Dollars for students. (If I haven&#x2019;t made my point clear, then let me explain in more general terms: you should come.)&#xD;&#xD;And now I&#x2019;m currently sitting here, awaiting my resplendent journey to class in about an hour while listening to an album which feels like ages ago that I&#x2019;ve listened to. And I just bought it towards the end of summer, which also feels like ages ago&#x2026; It invokes some self-established notions that I&#x2019;ve placed into the songs, those of which bring about some forlorn feelings. But they&#x2019;re not as omnipresent as they previously were. I&#x2019;m on to &lt;i&gt;bigger and better things, &lt;/i&gt;if you will. Things seem like they might be heading in a nice&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;direction currently in this respect, which is a nice change from the aforementioned formerly&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;present feelings&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&#xD;It&#x2019;s also getting to the point now where I just want this semester to end. I know I&#x2019;m not the only one who feels this way; I&#x2019;ve heard so many people say the same. While I&#x2019;m enjoying (most of) my current classes, I&#x2019;m just awaiting winter break. We&#x2019;re traveling&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to Florida again to visit &lt;i&gt;The Fam, &lt;/i&gt;which will be fun. Getting to see everyone again will be nice. And also I have to fit in guitar lessons &lt;i&gt;and &lt;/i&gt;a winter session class during then. We&#x2019;ll see how that goes&#x2026;&#xD;&#xD;You know, I&#x2019;ve also just realized that it feels good to write sometimes, even if there&#x2019;s nothing really to write about.&#xD;I guess that&#x2019;s why I have this blog in the first place! My investment in this domain name was not for naught after all!</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
