<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="0FB09E79-11AC-43CC-A8E0-1909C4CD9675">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120403" date="2012-04-03 23:00:03 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The Educational System is Flawed.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;November 28, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I just knew I was going to be kicking myself in the ass for not pass/no crediting that God-awful physics class I&#x2019;m currently in. I recently discovered that in order to be able to even pass the class, you need to have a &#x201C;passing average&#x201D; in the three tests given before any other work done in the class is even calculated into your grade. And these tests do not at all correlate with the material actually &lt;i&gt;learned &lt;/i&gt;in the class in the first place, while everything else that doesn&#x2019;t matter unless you pass these test does. Thus far, I seem to be on the track for failure, seeing as the first test was a huge wtf-moment, as well was the second, despite me feeling oh so confident about knowing the material. (Best part is: I actually &lt;i&gt;do &lt;/i&gt;know all the stuff we&#x2019;ve learned, it&#x2019;s just too bad we&#x2019;re not actually tested on whether we know it or not!) &#xD;&#xD;So at this rate, if I don&#x2019;t miraculously obtain pretty much a perfect score on the final, I&#x2019;ll fail the class despite my good grades in the labs which would have otherwise probably helped my overall grade if they would have counted! And then that big ol&#x2019; &lt;b&gt;F&lt;/b&gt; on my transcript will bring my GPA plummeting to its doom despite the multitude of &lt;b&gt;A&lt;/b&gt;s I&#x2019;ve received so far! Because, the things you do &lt;i&gt;well &lt;/i&gt;on hardly matter at all; it&#x2019;s only when you do bad, even on one thing, that you face the repercussions. And &lt;i&gt;then &lt;/i&gt;you get kicked out of school for your below-average GPA, sending your life into a miserable spiral of failure, lacking the morale to then ever go back and get that education you need in order to even achieve anything in this life and survive! &#xD;&#xD;I really do think we&#x2019;re too obsessed with grades over the actual quality of education. Now, this &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;could &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;be fine if only the tests that yield these grades accurately tested you on how much of the material you&#x2019;ve actually learned.&#xD;You know, this could all be seen as one huge elaborate plot by the education system to take your money, fail you, and then take your money again when you attempt to try again.&#xD;&#xD;I am so cynical and I love it. As well as bitter. Props go to Kenny for determining this vocabulary term to fit my current disposition.</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
